{
    "subject": "resource/S\u00e1nchez_Ram\u00edrez_Province",
    "predicate": "ontology/capital",
    "object": "resource/Cotu\u00ed",
    "human_readable": "The capital of S\u00e1nchez Ram\u00edrez Province is Cotu\u00ed.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9807332754135132,
            "question": "What is the capital of S\u00e1nchez Ram\u00edrez Province?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9288703799247742,
            "question": "What is the name of the province that Cotu\u00ed is the capital of?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7913340926170349,
            "question": "What are some other cities in S\u00e1nchez Ram\u00edrez Province?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6638199687004089,
            "question": "Is Cotu\u00ed a city?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6179143786430359,
            "question": "Where is Cotu\u00ed located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3574177622795105,
            "question": "Is there a major industry in Cotu\u00ed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3330534100532532,
            "question": "What is the population of Cotu\u00ed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.29097068309783936,
            "question": "How do people get around in Cotu\u00ed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21053944528102875,
            "question": "What are some cultural attractions in Cotu\u00ed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20490561425685883,
            "question": "Name a province in the Dominican Republic."
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The capital of S\u00e1nchez Ram\u00edrez Province is Cotu\u00ed.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9098_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some cultural attractions in Cotu\u00ed?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9098_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How do people get around in Cotu\u00ed?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9098_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the population of Cotu\u00ed?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9098_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9098_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9098_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9098_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9098_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9098_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9098_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9098_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9098_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9098_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9098_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I can conclude that:\n\n* The city of Cotu\u00ed is indeed mentioned in multiple documents as the capital of the S\u00e1nchez Ram\u00edrez province.\n* The location and geographical coordinates of Cotu\u00ed are also provided, which further supports its identification as a specific city.\n\nTherefore, based on the available information, I would answer:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that the city of Cotu\u00ed is indeed the capital of the S\u00e1nchez Ram\u00edrez province in the Dominican Republic, supporting the given statement."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}